-Hi, Beto.
-What's up?
-How are you?
-Not so good.
I've been here for 5min,
and no one came.
But it's full of waiters.
-Yes, but look. Hey, buddy!
-What are you doing?
You touched his arm?
You're not in the subway.
There's a way
to approach them.
Approach them?
I want a beer. It's their job.
-Hey, buddy!
-Don't talk like that to Toño.
His name is Toño?
-Toño, come here, please.
-No, stop.
Toño likes to be won over.
Won over? How?
-Make him jealous?
-How will I do that?
With Sergio,
the waiter with the beard.
Toño is jealous of Sergio.
Say something nice about him.
Suck up to him, go for it.
Okay.
-Sergio is the best waiter here.
-Yes, the best.
It's working, see?
I read in a magazine that Sergio
is the best waiter in Mexico.
Sergio, can I have a beer?
What are you doing?
That's cheating.
You've got Toño.
Pretend you're ignoring him,
that you can't see him.
I've never seen Toño
so crazy for someone.
What? I don't understand.
What should I do?
Take the menu.
Take it and look at him.
Look at him slowly.
Seduce him.
Look at him as if you'll order
something expensive.
What is it?
Shellfish? Crawfish?
Look at the menu then at him.
Now we'll do something risky.
You'll raise your hand. Raise it.
Raise your hand slowly.
Slowly. Now call him.
That's it. Act naturally.
-Hello.
-What's your name, sir?
-Toño.
Toño.
Toño?
Are you from here?
You sound from Colonia Doctores.
-No, I'm from Obrera.
-Beautiful!
I go there a lot.
-Can I be less formal?
-Yes, of course.
Toño, what do you like
to drink?
Juice.
-Juice?
-Yes.
Delicious.
But, for example,
if you were in a bar.
Well, in this case, beer.
I really like beer.
-I drink a lot of beer.
-What a coincidence!
We love beer too.
Listen, Toño dear...
If you happen to pass by the bar -
no pressure -,
could you maybe bring us
a couple of beers?
Any beer?
-Well, preferably...
-Yes.
-Yes, any beer. Okay.
-Yes, of course.
-Thanks.
-Sure.
Well done!
What an idiot!
I forgot to order food.
Don't worry.
They'll send chicken fried steak.
How?
My match on Tinder
is Rubén, the chef.
-Dude!
-I'm a dog!
It didn't work with Toño.
No, you should try Leo,
he's a man whore.
He swaps sides
whenever you ask.
-You can tip him anywhere.
-Leo!